(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
Omaru Polka Birthday Celebration 2026
新曲のお披露目あり！ 「Glitter Love」
New song debut! "Glitter Love"
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名
Polka's live with the most guests ever: 10 Holomembers
Glitter of Love
遥か天空 響いている
Echoing in the distant sky...
祈りは
...the prayer...
奇跡に
...turns into a miracle.
ETERNAL BLAZE
真夜中の蒼に溶けて
Melting into the blue of the midnight...
流れてく涙の粒
...droplets of flowing tears.
迷いなく包み込む
Wrapped without hesitation...
温もりに出逢った
...I met a warmth.
真っ白な雪のように
Like pure white snow...
どこまでも素直なコトバ
...words that are honest to the end.
鉄の羽根纏った
The iron wings I wore...
僕を動かしてく
...push me forward.
傷つくたびに
Every time I get hurt...
優しくなれる
...I become kinder.
君のその笑顔だけ
Only your smile...
守り抜きたい
...I want to protect till the end.
願いはひとつ
The wish is but one.
時空を越え刻まれた
Carved across time and space...
悲しみの記憶
...are memories of sadness.
まっすぐに受け止める
You accept it straight...
君は光の女神
...as the angel of light.
あの日胸に灯った
The eternal flame...
永遠の炎
...that was lit in my chest that day.
深い闇解き放って
Unleashing the deep darkness...
自由のトビラ開いてく
...opening the door to freedom...
強く果てない未来へ
...to a strong and endless future.
冷たい緑の月に
Upon the cold green moon...
映し出すココロの影
...reflecting the shadows of my heart...
淋し気に呟いた
...I whispered lonely,
「君のそばにいたい」
“I want to be by your side.”
真実と向き合うこと
Facing the truth...
教えてくれた勇気は
...the courage you taught me...
僕を駆け巡って
...runs through me...
希望に目覚めていく
...awakening to my dreams.
触れ合う気持ち
So that our touching feelings...
離れないように
...will never separate,
しっかりと抱きしめて
I hold them tightly...
確かな想い
...and pierce through...
貫いてゆく
...these certain thoughts.
銀の海に隠した
Hidden in the silver sea...
空白のページ
...is a blank page.
君だけが知っている
Show me the “truth”...
「本当」を僕に見せて
...that only you know.
吹き荒れる切なさに
From the raging heartache...
生まれゆく誓い
...a vow is born.
もう何も恐くはないよ
I'm not afraid of anything anymore,
結んだ視線そらさずに
without averting my eyes...
大切な「今」始める
...starting our precious “now.”
君が君でいられる場所
The place where you can be yourself...
悪夢にさらわれぬように
...so as not to be carried away by illusions...
消えない雨の苦しみも
Even the suffering of the never-ending rain,
鍵を壊してぶつけてよ
break the key and throw it at me,
隣にいるから
because I am right by your side.
すべてを信じて
Believe in everything.
時空を越え刻まれた
Carved across time and space...
悲しみの記憶
...are memories of sadness.
まっすぐに受け止める
You accept it straight...
君は光の女神
...as the angel of light.
あの日胸に灯った
The eternal flame...
永遠の炎
...that was lit in my chest that day.
深い闇解き放って
Unleashing the deep darkness...
自由のトビラ開いてく
...opening the door to freedom...
強く果てない未来へ
...to a strong and endless future.
解き放って
Release...
自由の扉開いてく
...and open the door of freedom!
強く果てない未来へ
To a strong and boundless future!
そうきっとここから始まる
Yes, it will surely begin from here!
お待たせみんな！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
今年もポルカの誕生日が始まった！
This year's Polka birthday has begun!
タイトルは、あ、かっこいい「Glitter Love」
The title is, oh so cool, 'Glitter Love'!
というわけで、ハッシュタグはこちら！
So, here is the hashtag!
尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
#OmaruPolkaBirthday2026
でいっぱい、いっぱい呟いてね！
Tweet lots and lots with it!
はい！
Yes!
いや、今回のテーマがまず
First of all, the theme this time is...
愛と勇気と戦う女の子になってます！
...about a girl who fights with love and courage!
そして、見てくださいこのステージ！
And take a look at this stage!
うわー！
Wow!
すごーい広い！
It's so spacious!
うわー！
Wow!
なんとですね、広いんですけれど
It's actually spacious, but first,
まずスクリーンが超巨大！
the screen is super huge!
大迫力！
Very powerful!
なんと、なんと、いつもの3倍くらい頑張りました！
We worked about three times harder than usual!
いや、頑張ってもらいました！
Or rather, they worked hard for me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
というわけでですね、ここからゲストの方々が
So, from here on, we have many guests...
たくさんいらっしゃいます！
...who will be joining us!
もうホロメンだけの歌だったら
If we're talking about Hololive members alone,
多分尾丸ポルカ史上最多のゲスト数だと
this is probably the most guests in Omaru Polka's history!
思っております！
That's what I think!
それをね、これからノンストップでお送りするので
We'll be presenting them non-stop from now on,
楽しんでいってください！
so please enjoy!
というわけで、いくぞー！
With that said, here we go!
遺伝子レベルの
On a genetic level,
インディペンデンス
Independence!
絶望も希望も
Despair and hope,
抱いて
embrace them!
足掻け 命尽きるまで
Struggle, until your life runs out!
光と飛沫のキス 恋のような
A kiss of light and spray, like love,
虹のバースデイ
a rainbow birthday
どんな美しき日も
On any beautiful day,
何か生まれ 何かが死ぬ
something is born and something dies
せめて歌を (I love you)
At least a song (I love you)
世界がヒドい地獄だとしても
even if the world is a terrible hell
せめて伝えよう (I love you)
At least let me tell you (I love you)
最後の 刻は来た
the final moment has come
星振る 天へと 響き飛べリバティソング
Echo and fly toward the starlit heavens, song of liberty!
スターダスト！
Stardust!
そして奇跡は待つものじゃなくて
And miracles aren't something to wait for,
その手で作るものと吠えろ
howl that they are made with your own hands!
涙した過去をレクイエムにして
Turn the tearful past into a requiem
聖なる全部の力で
with all your holy power,
輝けフューチャー
shine, future!
信じて照らせ 星天ギャラクシィクロス
Believe and illuminate, Seiten Galaxy Cross!
一人じゃないことを
That you are not alone,
やがて君は
you will soon...
知る日のため
...come to know one day
指先伝う波動
The waves traveling through your fingertips
分かち合って
share them,
明日に向かう 永遠なる空に
To the eternal sky heading toward tomorrow,
(I feel you)
自由の魂は 殺せはしない
The soul of freedom cannot be killed,
不滅なる夢に
in this immortal dream,
(I feel you)
体温と 剣を握れ
Grasp warmth and your sword,
運命の終局も 絶ち切る力で
with the power to cut through even the end of destiny!
きらめき...
Glittering...
十字となって闇を暴く！
Becoming a cross to expose the darkness!
駆け抜けた丘には...
On the hill we ran through...
神様も知らない...
Even God doesn't know...
歴史が息づき...
History comes alive...
誇る！
and prides itself!
My tough and brave heart!
この絆、
With this bond,
星天ギャラクシィクロス！
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
逆光の翼で
With wings against the light,
Just believe!
焦がれる炎で
With a burning flame,
Big mission!
覚悟を背負い戦おう！
Let's carry our resolve and fight!
そして奇跡を待つものじゃなくて...
And we are not those who just wait for miracles...
その手で作るものと吠えろ！
Howl that they are something we make with our own hands!
何分だって何分だって
No matter how many times, no matter how many times,
立ち上がろうか？
shall we stand up again?
聖なる全部の力で
With all of our sacred power,
輝く future!
a shining future!
信じて照らせ！
Believe and illuminate!
星天ギャラクシィクロス！
Seiten Galaxy Cross!
Let's sing! Let's spin! Let's dance! Let's fun! Let's smile! Let's fly! Precure!
Let's sing! Let's spin! Let's dance! Let's fun! Let's smile! Let's fly!
ときめき出会い交わして世界...
Exchange heart-fluttering encounters, world...
未来、1+1+1は無限！
Future, 1 + 1 + 1 is infinite!
唇からこぼれる歌は...
The songs spilling from our lips...
プリズム眩しい光反射、
Reflecting the dazzling prism light,
三人寄れば文殊最高最強！
three people together make the best, strongest wisdom!
始まるただ一つのライブ Enjoy together!
The one and only live show begins, enjoy together!
ハミング！
Humming!
助走して！
Take a running start!
カンバセーション コール&レスポンス！
Conversation, call & response!
輝くフレーズいいよね！
The shining phrases are great, aren't they?
好きな好きなフレーズを、
Our favorite, favorite phrases,
シンフォニーに夢のせて君とあなたの元へ For you!
carrying our dreams in a symphony to you and yours, for you!
もっともっと輝きあえるね、みんなで！
We can shine brighter and brighter together, everyone!
One, two, three!
スクリーンにいつだって笑顔写しあおう！
Let's always reflect our smiles on the screen!
Show me!
君がいるからパワー生まれるよ今日も！
Because you are here, power is born again today!
Trio Dreams!
Let's sing! Let's spin! Let's dance! Let's fun! Let's smile! Let's fly!
一緒だから感じるハッピーワンダフル、
Because we are together, we feel happy, wonderful!
1×1×1は無敵！
1 × 1 × 1 is invincible!
出し惜しみはなしで全部あげたい！
No holding back, we want to give you everything!
ハプニングさえもチョイスワンダフル、
Even happenings are a wonderful choice!
三人寄れば文殊面白そう！
Three people together make it look interesting!
見せるよきっと伝説のライブ...
We'll surely show you a legendary live...
アンコール頂戴！
Give us an encore!
ユーモア！
Humor!
ポップアップ！
Pop up!
セッション オール・ウェルカム！
Session, all welcome!
カテゴリーなんていらないよね！
We don't need categories, do we?
好きな好きな思い切り...
With our favorite, favorite all...
上昇する羽広げて ハートの奥の奥へ Hurry up!
Spreading our rising wings, to the deep depths of your heart, hurry up!
命は輝きでできているの！
Life is made of brilliance!
Yeah! Yeah!
ビートスリーンの向こうはみ出しちゃう 嬉しい楽しい Surprise!
The beat spills past the screen, happy and fun, surprise!
君を知って知らない自分に会えたよ Trio Dreams!
By knowing you, I met a self I didn't know, Trio Dreams!
Let's sing! Let's spin! Let's dance! Let's fun! Let's smile! Let's fly!
みんな一緒に！Let's sing! Let's spin! Let's dance! Let's fun! Let's smile! Let's fly!
Everyone together! Let's sing! Let's spin! Let's dance! Let's fun! Let's smile! Let's fly!
輝くフレーズいいよね！
The shining phrases are great, aren't they?
好きな好きなフレーズを、
Our favorite, favorite phrases,
シンフォニーに夢のせて君とあなたの元へ For you!
carrying our dreams in a symphony to you and yours, for you!
もっともっと輝きあえるね、みんなで！
We can shine brighter and brighter together, everyone!
瞳 水晶
Eyes... crystal...
スクリーンに
...on the screen,
いつまでも 笑顔映し合おう
let's always reflect our smiles on each other.
キミが
Because you...
いるからパワー
...are here, power...
生まれるよ、今日も
...is born today as well!
Try try trio dreams
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance!
Let's bound! Let's smile! Let's fly!
Woo... Recieve!!!
Woo... Receive!!!
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance!
Let's bound! Let's smile! Let's fly!
暗闇のまんなか
Right in the middle of the darkness,
真っ直ぐな眼差しで
with a steady, direct gaze...
立ち上がる姿 ちゃんと見ていたよ保存
I saw you clearly as you stood up.
閉じ込められそうな
Rouse your heart,
心を奮い立たせ
that feels like it's about to be locked away...
おさまりきらない 輝きを放ち
...and release an uncontainable brilliance!
射抜かれた胸のおく
Deep within my pierced heart,
焼きついた目映さは
that dazzling brightness is burned in.
それだけでも もう理由になる
That alone is reason enough,
待っていて
so wait for me.
取り戻したい |
We want to bring back...
光の世界
...the world of light!
その笑顔
That smile,
勇気 涙 夢 希望の兆し
courage, tears, dreams—signs of hope.
キミと明日を願う
With the power of wishing...
チカラから
...for tomorrow with you,
our harmony is born.
うまれる 私たちのハーモニー
Let it resonate!
響け
それでも暗闇は
Even so, darkness...
訪れてしまうもの
...is bound to visit us.
惑わされないさ
But we won't be led astray,
キミはキミだから
because you are who you are.
重ね合えた日々が
The days we've shared together...
ハートを輝かせる
...make our hearts shine.
ひとりじゃないこと 気付かせてくれる
They remind me that I'm not alone.
抱えきれないほどの
In place of...
「ありがとう」の代わりに
...an overwhelming "thank you,"
鍵を掛けて
let's lock it away...
ひとつになる
...and become one.
受け止めて
Accept it!
取り戻すんだ
We will bring back...
光の未来
...the future of light!
いま熱く
Right now, passionately...
想い繋ぐから
...I'll connect our feelings,
叶えに行くよ
so we can make it come true!
キミと一緒に
Together with you...
願えるキセキ
...the miracles we wish for...
重ねて
...will overlap,
広がっていく ハーモニー
and our harmony will spread!
目覚めるときが来たね
The time to awaken has come.
本当の自分になる
We will become our true selves,
満ちる 運命
and fulfill our destiny!
取り戻したい
We want to bring back...
光の世界
...the world of light!
その笑顔
That smile,
勇気 涙 夢 希望の兆し
courage, tears, dreams—signs of hope.
キミと明日を
With the power of wishing...
願えるチカラから うまれる
...for tomorrow with you,
私たちのハーモニー
our harmony is born.
響け
Let it resonate!
Day by day 日に日に募るの 乙女心
Day by day, my girlish feelings grow stronger and stronger.
同じ...
The same...
おんなじクラス 斜め前のおとなしい人
The quiet person in the same class, sitting diagonally in front of me
カッコ良くはない だけど優しい
Not cool, but kind
いつも頼れる 彼
The one I can always rely on
After school 恋愛相談の帰り道
After school, on the way back from romantic advice
なんだって話せる 親友の女の子
The best friend girl I can tell anything to
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて
Good at sports, good at studying
女子力MAXです
Max femininity
どこにでもある よくあること
It happens everywhere, it's a common occurrence
急に彼女が
Suddenly she says,
「あのね、実は私 好きな人がいるの…！」って
"You know, actually, I have someone I like...!"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangle, love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
The balance crumbles in an instant, in an instant
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A trope like in a cheesy manga
まさかね 自分が立てちゃうなんて
No way, I'm the one who set it up?
残念すぎます！
That's too disappointing!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangle, love is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category that can't be resolved with "just kidding"
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship swaying, swaying
なんか青春しちゃいます
I'm having a youthful moment
わたし 困っちゃいます
I'm troubled
完敗です！お似合いすぎるわ 勝てっこない
I'm completely defeated! They're too perfect, I can't win
くやしいけどとか そんなんじゃなくて本心
It's not that I'm jealous or anything, it's my true feelings
てゆーか すでに応援モード
Actually, I'm already in support mode
むしろ 清々しい
If anything, it's refreshing
だけど彼女は 不思議な顔
But she has a strange look on her face
真剣な目で
With serious eyes, she says,
「そうじゃなくて、私 あなたが好き…ゴメン」って
"That's not it, I like you... sorry"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, seriously!?
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangle, love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
The balance crumbles in an instant, in an instant
わたし アナタ 彼女とわたし
Me, you, her, and me
超絶！複雑！百合展開は 想定外です！
Extremely! Complex! A Yuri development is unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangle, love is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category that can't be resolved with "just kidding"
解けないパズル 与え給うた
An unsolvable puzzle given to me
神よ 恨んじゃいます
God, I hate you
わたし 悩んじゃいます
I'm suffering
「あーっ！もう！スゴいヤバい！」
"Aah! Already! This is crazy, bad!"
「好きだよ？好きだけど…って、そういう意味じゃなくって！」
"I like you? I like you but... wait, I didn't mean it in that way!"
「だって…女の子同士だし…」
"Because... we're both girls..."
「ねえ 神様、どうしたらいいの？」
"Hey God, what should I do?"
「わたし、どうしたいの？」
"What do I want to do?"
「ヘルプミ〜〜〜！！！」
"Help me~~~!!!"
なんか変だー
Something is weird
愛に国境も 歳も 性別も カンケーない！
Love has no borders, age, or gender!
けど、けど、けど！
But, but, but!
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, triangle, love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれるバランス
The balance crumbles in an instant, in an instant
普通の恋 夢みてたのに
I was dreaming of a normal love
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃ ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます！
With my normal settings, it's a bit too much of a impossible game!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, triangle, love is unstable
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category that can't be resolved with "just kidding"
彼女のこと 好きになれたら
If I could come to like her
なんて妄想しちゃいます
I'm fantasizing about that
…わたし どうかしちゃってます
...I've gone crazy
劫々とつづくショートショート
The endless, repeating short stories continue
喪失は絶対零度だ
Loss is absolute zero
今夜はリィンカーネーション
Tonight is reincarnation
哀しみが
Sadness is...
混沌の子守唄うたってるよ
...singing a lullaby of chaos
運命に理由があるのならば
If there is a reason for fate,
すべてを賭けてみたいの
I want to bet everything on it
あなたを守りたい
I want to protect you
どこまでも高く飛べるわ
I can fly higher and higher, to anywhere
どこまでも強く強くなれるわ
I can become stronger and stronger, to anywhere
信じて わたしに 出会えたキセキ
Believe in the miracle of meeting me
切り開くは、不死鳥の炎
The one that blazes a path is the phoenix's flame
説いて あなたのドグマ
Explain your dogma
blackout blackout
眼差しに泣きたくなるの
Your gaze makes me want to cry
flashback flashback
振りほどけ ascend
Shake it off and ascend
挑み続けろ
Keep on challenging
飄々と佇むホット・ショット
An aloof and detached hot shot
わたしが必要でしょ?
You need me, don't you?
今夜はリィンカーネーション
Tonight is reincarnation
正しさが
Righteousness...
ストレイシープ最前線に押し出すよ
...pushes the stray sheep to the very front line
運命に理由があるのならば
If there is a reason for fate,
優しい世界をあげたい
I want to give you a kind world
あなたを包むわ
I will embrace you
どこまでも速く射抜くわ
I will shoot through, faster than anywhere
どこまでも熱く熱く焦がすわ
I will burn, hotter and hotter, to anywhere
信じて わたしに 出会えたキセキ
Believe in the miracle of meeting me
切り開くは、不死鳥の炎
The one that blazes a path is the phoenix's flame
説いて あなたのドグマ
Explain your dogma
blackout blackout
肩越しに光を見せて
Show me the light over your shoulder
flashback flashback
許さない betray
I won't forgive a betray
進み続けろ 尽きるまで
Keep moving forward until the end
傍にいると
When I'm by your side...
鼓動が速くて 目眩がする
...my heart beats fast, and I feel dizzy
全て捧げる
I'll offer everything
もう決めたの
I've already decided
最後のチャンスだから
Because this is the last chance...
もう離さない
...I won't let go anymore
あなたに潜る
Diving into you
未来の風が
The wind of the future
混ざり合っていく
Is mixing together
神様に恋をしてた頃は
When I was in love with God,
こんな別れが来るとは思ってなかったよ
I never thought such a parting would come.
もう二度と触れられないなら
If we can never touch again,
せめて最後に もう一度抱きしめて欲しかったよ
At least one last time, I wish you had held me close.
It's long long good-bye...
さよなら さよなら 何度だって
Good-bye, good-bye, no matter how many times...
自分に 無上に 言い聞かせて
I tell myself, so heartlessly.
手を振るのは 優しさだよね?
Is waving my hand a kindness?
今強さが欲しい
I want strength now.
貴方に出会い STAR輝いて アタシが生まれて
Meeting you, the star shone, and I was born.
愛すればこそ iあればこそ
Because I love, because I exist.
希望のない 奇跡を待って どうなるの?
Waiting for a miracle without hope, what will become of it?
涙に滲む 惑星の瞬きは gone...
In my tears, the planet's twinkling is gone...
忘れないよ 貴方の温もりも
I won't forget your warmth,
その優しさも 全て包んでくれた両手も
Or your kindness, or your hands that embraced everything.
It's long long good-bye...
さよなら さよなら 愛しい人
Good-bye, good-bye, my beloved...
貴方が いたから 歩いてこれた
Because you were here, I could walk on.
ひとりなんかじゃなかったよね?
I wasn't alone, was I?
今答えが欲しい
I want an answer now.
燃える様な流星 捕まえて 火を灯して
Catch a burning meteor, light a fire.
愛していたい 愛されてたい
I want to love, I want to be loved.
冷えたカラダひとつで 世界は どうなるの?
With just this cold body, what will become of the world?
張り続けてた 虚勢が溶けてく long for...
The bravado I kept holding onto melts away, long for...
どうしてなの? 涙溢れて 止められない
Why? Tears overflow, I cannot stop them.
貴方に出会い STAR輝いて アタシが生まれて
Meeting you, the star shone, and I was born.
愛すればこそ iあればこそ
Because I love, because I exist.
希望のない 奇跡を待って どうなるの?
Waiting for a miracle without hope, what will become of it?
涙に滲む 惑星の瞬きは gone...
In my tears, the planet's twinkling is gone...
もし生まれ変わって また巡り会えるなら
If I am reborn and we can meet again...
その時もきっと アタシを見つけ出して
I am sure, please find me again then too.
もう二度と離さないで 捕まえてて
Don't let go of me ever again, hold onto me.
ひとりじゃないと
That I am not alone...
囁いてほしい プラネット
Whisper it to me, Planet
聖なる瞳が 痛みを映したら
If my saint-like eyes reflect pain...
振り向いてごらん？ 情熱放つ trick
Will you look back? A passion-releasing trick
崩れる足元 二人は戻れない
Our crumbling footing, we two can't return
差し伸べた手をほどかないで
Don't let go of my outstretched hand
消えるよ また優しい日々が
Those tender days have disappeared once again
思い出を汚すのは許せない
I won't allow our memories to be tainted
ここは裏切りの楽園 さ迷う心の涯に
This is the paradise of betrayal, at the end of my wandering heart
光を求めて 祈る言葉届け あなたに
Searching for the light, I pray these words reach you
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
These imprisoned wings head towards the distant sky
信じたいよ 私たち孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we are not alone
分かり合う (求め合う) 絆の中
Understanding each other (seeking each other) within this bond
離さない (離れない) 始まる destiny
I won't let go (I won't separate), our destiny begins
新たな願いに 鎖ほどける時
With a new wish, when our chains are removed
休ませてくれる？ 深い眠りに
Will you let me rest? In a deep sleep...
僅かな希望が 私を強くする
This small hope makes me strong
ぬくもりに触れてみたいから
Because I want to feel your warmth
蘇れば 儚きいのち
If resurrected, this fleeting life...
繰り返す愛しさが 導いた
Led by a love that repeats over and over
胸に泡沫の調べ 流れる世界の終わり
A transient melody in my heart, at the end of this flowing world
諦めはしない 今が繋ぐ明日探そう
I won't give up, let's search for tomorrow connected by today
ちぎれ舞う羽は 未来の空にも向かう
Torn wings fluttering, heading towards the sky of the future
忘れないで 私たちひとつの水晶
Don't forget, we are a single crystal
輝いて (眩しくて) 割れないのよ
Shining (dazzling), we won't shatter
離さない (離れない) 誓いの destiny
I won't let go (I won't separate), our promised destiny
Lost the paradise...
消えるよ また優しい日々が
Those tender days have disappeared once again
思い出を汚すのは許せない
I won't allow our memories to be tainted
ここは裏切りの楽園 さ迷う心の涯に
This is the paradise of betrayal, at the end of my wandering heart
光を求めて 祈る言葉届け あなたに
Searching for the light, I pray these words reach you
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
These imprisoned wings head towards the distant sky
信じたいよ 私たち孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we are not alone
分かり合う (求め合う) 絆の中
Understanding each other (seeking each other) within this bond
離さない (離れない)
I won't let go (I won't separate)...
離さない
Don't let go...
見つめて Paradise Lost
Stare at me, Paradise Lost.
(Wow wow wow wow...)
やっとみんな会えたね
We finally all met!
don't stop！no,don't stop ’til finish！！
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
(wo oh oh)
don't stop！no,don't stop ’til finish！！
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
(wo oh oh)
たかたった全力走りたい
Galloping along, I want to run at full speed!
芝と砂とキミの追い切りメニュー
Turf, dirt, and your final training plan.
turn up！(turn up！）
Turn up! (Turn up!)
声出せ叫べ(wo oh oh)
Raise your voice and shout (wo oh oh)!
それせーの！ファイ！(オー！)ファイ！(オー！)
Ready, set, go! Fight! (Oh!) Fight! (Oh!)
たかたった全力上がりタイム
Galloping along, giving it my all in the final stretch!
ゆずれない夢の途中(wow wow)
In the middle of our unyielding dream (wow wow)...
始めようここから最高story
let's start the greatest story from here.
(wow wow wow)
(o oh o oh...おっおっおーー！)
(O oh o oh... Oh, oh, oh!)
あこがれの地へ(勇気すこし借りて)
To the land of our dreams (borrowing a little courage)...
語り合ったmemory(二度と来ない今を)
the memories we shared (cherishing this fleeting moment).
もうドキドキもトキメキも抑えられないたまんない
I can't contain the excitement and fluttering anymore!
熱いハラハラが止まらない
The thrilling suspense won't stop!
キミと走り競いゴール目指し
With you, racing together, aiming for the finish line...
遥か響け届けmusic
resound far and wide, reach us, music!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い夢がきっと叶うなら
My feelings forever and ever... if our dream will surely come true,
あの日キミに感じた何かを信じて
believing in that something I felt from you that day.
春も夏も秋も冬も超え願い焦がれ走れ
Overcoming spring, summer, autumn, and winter, longing and running...
ah勝利へ
Ah, toward victory!
don't stop！no,don't stop ’til finish！！
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
(wo oh oh)
don't stop！no,don't stop ’til finish！！
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
(wo oh oh)
たかたった全力はじけたい
Galloping along, I want to burst with energy!
期待出会い決意キズナになった
Expectations, meetings, and determinations turned into bonds.
hands up！(hands up！)
Hands up! (Hands up!)
本気で叫べ(wo oh oh)
Scream with all your might (wo oh oh)!
それせーの！ファイ！(オー！)ファイ！(オー！)
Ready, set, go! Fight! (Oh!) Fight! (Oh!)
たかたった全力笑いたい
Galloping along, I want to laugh with all my heart!
ターフのど真ん中(wow wow)
Right in the middle of the turf (wow wow)...
リアルにここから上昇story
in reality, the rising story starts from here.
(wow wow wow)
(o oh o oh...おっおっおーー！)
(O oh o oh... Oh, oh, oh!)
駆け抜けた日々(昨日よりも今日を)
The days we ran through (today more than yesterday)...
語り合ったglory(強くなれる理由)
the glory we talked about (the reason we can become stronger).
いま応えたい「生きてる」と
Right now, I want to respond, 'I'm alive!'
背中押す声熱くなる
The voice pushing my back gets passionate.
夢は夢のまま終われない
A dream cannot end just as a dream!
キミと未来描きゴール目指し
With you, drawing the future, aiming for the finish line...
狙え挑め掴めwinning
aim, challenge, and grasp winning!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い夢はきっと叶うから
My feelings forever and ever... because dreams will surely come true,
あの日キミが流した涙も信じて
believing even in the tears you shed that day.
雨も風も雲も闇も超え願い焦がれ走れ
Overcoming rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, longing and running...
ah勝利へ
Ah, toward victory!
ゆるぎない覚悟決して
An unyielding determination, definitely...
1つ2つ共に綴る記録
writing down records together, one by one.
背中に迫る迷い振り払え
Shake off the hesitation creeping up behind you...
今の自分追い越すだけ
just overtake who you are right now.
勝ちたい勝ちたい勝ちたいキミと勝ちたい
I want to win, I want to win, I want to win, with you!
ファイ！ファイ！ファイ！
Fight! Fight! Fight!
未来描きゴール目指し狙え挑め掴めwinning
Drawing the future, aiming for the finish line, aim, challenge, and grasp winning!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い夢はきっと叶うから
My feelings forever and ever... because dreams will surely come true,
あの日キミが流した涙も信じて
believing even in the tears you shed that day.
春も夏も秋も冬も超え雨も風も超え雲も闇も超え
Overcoming spring, summer, autumn, and winter, rain and wind, clouds and darkness...
勝利へ
Toward victory!
キミと
With you,
走り競いゴール目指し
racing together, aiming for the finish line,
遥か響け届けmusic
resound far and wide, reach us, music!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い夢がきっと叶うなら
My feelings forever and ever... if our dream will surely come true,
あの日キミに感じた何かを信じて
believing in that something I felt from you that day.
春も夏も秋も冬も超え願い焦がれ走れ
Overcoming spring, summer, autumn, and winter, longing and running...
夏も秋も冬も超え願い焦がれ走れ
Even through summer, autumn, and winter, run with burning desire
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, to victory
未来描くロード目指し
Aiming for the road that draws the future
狙い 挑め 掴め winny
Aim, challenge, and seize victory!
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
My long-held, everlasting thoughts...
夢はきっと叶うから
...because our dreams will surely come true.
あの日のキミが流した
Those tears that you shed on that day...
涙も信じて
...believe in them too.
雨も風も雲も闇も超え願い焦がれ走れ
Beyond the rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, run with desire and yearning
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, to victory
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
STARTING OVER
作詞：こだまさおり
作曲・編曲：睦月周平
[STARTING OVER]
Lyrics: Saori Kodama
Composition & Arrangement: Shuhei Mutsuki
It's finally the true end
I'm ready for... my destiny
I'm ready for... STARTING OVER
やっと幕を下ろせた
I was finally able to lower the curtain
最後の瞬間まで
Until the very last moment,
わたしは精一杯に
I, with all my might,
わたしをやりきった
lived my life to the fullest.
終演の続きは
The sequel to this final curtain...
誰も知らなくていい
...is something no one needs to know.
涙を置いて
Leaving our tears behind,
新しい旅に出よう
let's set out on a new journey.
熱狂はあなたを選ぶ
The passion chooses you
違う結末だっただけ
it was simply a different ending.
同じ愛になれなかった Destiny
A destiny where we couldn't share the same love
これまでの全てを
It was a love where I would offer...
差し出すような愛だった
...everything I had up until now.
世界の意味が変わるくらいに
To the point where the meaning of the world changed,
肯定された気がしたんだ
I felt fully accepted.
何気なさの中で
Amidst the casual everyday moments,
気づけた最初の奇跡が
the first miracle I realized...
あなたでよかった わたしでよかった
...was how glad I am it was you, how glad I am it was me.
心から思えたよ
I could truly believe it from the bottom of my heart.
ずっと遠い未来も
Even in the far-off future,
ちゃんと覚えていよう
let's remember it properly.
自分の抱きしめかた
How to embrace myself,
明日の願いかた
and how to wish for tomorrow.
あなたがいなくても
Even if you are no longer here,
わたしの片隅で
in a corner of my heart,
優しい光
a gentle light...
消えたりしないとわかる
...I know will never fade away.
今はまだ手を振れるほど
Though our paths have only just split...
道は別れたばかりで
...to the point where I can still wave goodbye,
後ろ髪に風を感じながら
while feeling the wind in my hair from behind.
それまでの全てが
Everything up until that point...
あなたに出会うためだった
...was meant to lead me to you.
どの瞬間もムダじゃないこと
That not a single moment was in vain,
本当の意味で知れたから
I have finally learned its true meaning.
次の曲がり角も
At the next corner as well,
自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose my own way.
いつかに繋がる
Connecting to some day,
新しい一歩 信じて歩き出そう
let's believe in this new step and walk forward.
心から誰かを愛せた
That I was able to love someone from my heart...
あの日々は
...those days...
間違いなくわたしの Destiny Ah
...were without a doubt my Destiny, ah...
これまでの全てが
Everything up until now...
新しい力をくれる
...gives me new strength.
どの瞬間もムダじゃないなら
If not a single moment was in vain,
何が起きても大丈夫だから
then no matter what happens, I will be okay.
次の物語も
For the next story too,
自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose my own way.
いつかに繋がる
Connecting to some day,
わたしのはじまり 信じて歩き出そう
let's believe in my new beginning and walk forward.
の〜
...no...
再び幕は上がる
The curtain rises once more
聞いていただいたのは、新曲の「STARTING OVER」でした！
The song you just heard was my new song, "STARTING OVER"!
はい、新年一発目、新曲の初披露というわけで、ぬるっとね、新曲をやってしまったんですが
Yes, first thing in the new year, a premiere of a new song! So I kind of casually performed it...
平成感のある、懐かしみの感じの楽曲をこちらで歌わせていただいたんですけれども
I performed a song here that has a "Heisei era" feel and a nostalgic touch, but...
このあと、この曲が、24時から、あと、もう数時間か、24時からですね
After this, this song will be released from 24:00—just a few hours from now—yes, from 24:00...
1月30日の24時から、配信リリースされます！たくさん聞いてください！
On January 30th at midnight, it will be released digitally! Please listen to it a lot!
今年もね、たくさん、オリ曲出していきたいです！
This year as well, I want to release lots of original songs!
そしてそして、もうMCが、実は、最後なのでね、えーと、この配信のあとには
And also, this is actually the last MC segment, so after this stream...
メンバー限定の配信もあるので、よろしくお願いします！
we have a members-only stream, so please look forward to it!
よし、よし、よし。グッズ紹介！
All right, all right, all right. Merchandise introduction!
えー、ここには、同期のねぽらぼを大集合ということで、ね、ら、ぼ、集まれー！
For this, my genmates "Neporabo" are gathering here! Ne, Ra, Bo, come on out!
いぇーい！
Yay!
はい、ぽ、ぽ、ぽ、ぽ、初めて呼ばれました。どうも。
Yes, Po-Po-Po-Polka, I was invited here for the first time. Hello.
え、初だっけ？
Wait, is it the first time?
ぽるかチャンネル初です！
It's my first time on Polka's channel!
お誕生日おめでとう！ / ありがとう！ / おめでとう！
Happy Birthday! / Thank you! / Congratulations!
ここまでが流れでございます。はい。
This has been the routine so far. Yes.
待ってたよ。
We were waiting.
グッズを紹介させていただきたいと思います！みんなで見ながらリアクションをね...
I'd like to introduce the merchandise! I'd love it if everyone could watch and react...
了解した。 / がやがや。
Got it. / Chatter chatter.
というわけで、尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念グッズ2026、ラインナップはこちら！どん！
So, the lineup for Omaru Polka's Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise is here! Bam!
おー！すごーい！ / というわけで、素晴らしい今回のラインナップが揃っております！
Whoa, amazing! / So, we have a wonderful lineup this time!
え？すごい！ / あれ？ちょっと、あれ？ / あれれ？ / ちょっとおかしくない？
Huh? Wow! / Wait, a little bit...? / Huh? / Isn't there something off?
ちょっと、なんか、盛ってません？ / 盛ってませんよ！盛ってません！
Wait, isn't it kind of padded? / It's not padded! It's not!
というわけで、まずは一つ一つ動かしていきましょう！まずは、こちら！はい！
So, let's go through them one by one! First, this one! Yes!
ポルカの、初めての抱き枕カバーになっております！
This is Polka's very first body pillow cover!
え、ちょっとポルカさん、パンツ履いてなくない？ / あれ？丸出しじゃないですか？
Wait, Polka-san, aren't you not wearing panties? / Huh? Isn't it completely bare?
履いてる、履いてる！それ、部屋着だよ、部屋着！ / ねねのだってこういう部屋着だもん！
I'm wearing them, I am! That's loungewear! Loungewear! / But even Nene has this kind of loungewear!
ねねのも...？
Even Nene's...?
人のチャンネルだからって、やりたい放題チャンネルして！
Just because it's someone else's channel, you're doing whatever you want!
ほんま、シャツで寝たらシワつくぞ。 / シワつきます。写真撮影用かもしれないです！<
Seriously, if you sleep in a shirt, it will get wrinkled. / It will. Maybe it's just for the photo shoot!
というわけで、初めて抱き枕カバー出します。表が通常衣装で、裏は彼シャツになってます！
So, I'm releasing a body pillow cover for the first time. The front is the usual outfit, and the back is the boyfriend shirt!
かわいい！ / ありがとうございます！ / はい、ありがとうね、みんな！
Cute! / Thank you! / Yes, thank you everyone!
続きまして、ドン！こちら、歴代衣装のポルカランダムラバーストラップです！
Moving on, bam! Here is the Polka Random Rubber Strap in past outfits!
これまでの衣装のラバーストラップ、こちら「のいみね」先生に描いていただきました！
The rubber straps of past outfits, drawn by Noimine-sensei!
えっ、めっちゃいいじゃん、これ！ / どのお衣装が出るか、お楽しみです。ありがとうね！
Whoa, this is so good! / Look forward to seeing which outfit you get. Thank you!
続きまして、こちら！ドン！「どれもこれも宝物！思い出バインダー」！
Moving on, here! Bam! "Every single one is a treasure! Memory Binder"!
これですね、最近みんなも特典でチェキ風ブロマイドカード出してたりするから、そういうの入れられたり
For this, lately everyone has been releasing polaroid-style bromides as bonuses, so you can put those in,
あとはホロカも入るサイズになっておりますので、ぜひぜひ、いろんな思い出をしまってください！
and it's also sized to fit HoloKa cards, so please store all kinds of memories in it!
はい、そして続きましては、こちら！「ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー」！
Yes, and moving on, here! "Polka's Tail Keyholder"!
一周して流行ってるからね。ポルカのしっぽ柄のキーホルダー！
It's come full circle and is trendy now. A keyholder shaped like Polka's tail!
平成レトロみたいな感じで出しております。はい、こちらもつけてください！
We're releasing it with a Heisei retro vibe. Yes, please wear this too!
そしてボイスも出ます。ボイスはこちら！じゃん！ASMRボイスです。
And there's also a voice pack. Here it is! Ta-da! An ASMR voice.
はい、えーと、彼シャツのポルカ、というね、ちょっとタイトルもなんか... / 狙ってるじゃん
Yes, "Polka in a Boyfriend Shirt"... the title is also a bit... / You're totally aiming for that!
何で今日同期を呼んじゃったんだろうって、一瞬思った今。恥ずかしくなってきた。
I just wondered for a second why I invited my genmates today. I'm getting embarrassed.
勝て！ / 勝て勝て！ / う、う、う。ここ今、修羅場みたいになってる。
Fight! / Fight, fight! / U-U-U. It feels like a war zone here right now.
えーと、添い寝ASMRというか、抱き枕カバーとイラストの関係があるシチュエーションになってます！
So it's a co-sleeping ASMR, a situation connected to the illustration on the body pillow cover!
はい、皆さんお待たせしました。フルセット購入特典になっております。こちら！
Yes, thank you for waiting. This is the full set purchase bonus. Here!
チェキ風ブロマイドカード！数量限定が直筆メッセージ、箔押し複製サインになっております！
A polaroid-style bromide card! The limited quantity version has a handwritten message and a foil-stamped replica signature!
通常が箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りでございます！
The regular version has a foil-stamped replica signature and a printed message!
フルセットぜひぜひ買っていただいた方には、特典ボイスとして「すやすやポルカの、いちばん近い約束」...
For those who buy the full set, as a bonus voice, we have "Sleeping Polka's closest promise"...
一緒にね「寝ようね」みたいな感じのちょっとそういったボイスになってて
It's a voice track like "Let's sleep together,"
こっちもASMRになってます
and this one is also ASMR.
よろしくお願いしまーす
Please look forward to it!
恥ずかしいな、みんなとやるのこれ！
It's so embarrassing to do this with everyone!
なんかエッチな女になってるなって
I feel like I've become a sexy woman...
すいません、新年もね、皆さん改めてこれからよろしくお願いします
Sorry! Happy New Year, everyone. We look forward to working with you.
というわけで、今日はみんなで最後一緒に歌を歌うために呼んできたということで、準備してきます！
So today, I called everyone here to sing together at the end. We're going to get ready!
いってらっしゃーい！じゃ、こっちは盛り上がってねー！
See you! Have fun over there!
脚本は捨てちゃおっか
Shall we throw away the script?
さあしかと焼き付けよ！
Now, make sure to burn this into your memory!
アドリブの熱いパフォーマンス
This passionate, ad-libbed performance!
屋根裏を飛び出して
Leaving the attic behind,
壮大に響く特別なストーリー
a special story echoing magnificently!
瞼の裏には
Behind closed eyelids,
虹が紡ぐ
a rainbow weaves
星空のメモリー
memories of the starry sky.
等身大の愛を込めて
With life-sized love,
想像を超える世界へ
to a world beyond imagination!
誰も知らないでしょ
Nobody knows yet, right?
Are you ready?
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future awaits.
なんて自由だ！笑っちゃうよ
It's so free! It makes me laugh.
ねえホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, let's go beyond the hologram!
誰だって置いてかないよ
I won't leave anyone behind.
ごらん！歓声が呼んでいる
Look! The cheers are calling us.
スナップからパッと照らす
Lighting up in a snap,
人生のスポットライト
the spotlight of life.
薔薇色のプレミアショー
A rose-colored premium show!
ここが特等席よ
This is the best seat in the house!
本日ロマンス日和
Today is a perfect day for romance.
（天気次第のエチュード）
(An etude depending on the weather)
まるで絵物語
Just like a picture story.
捕まえてよ
Catch me!
（待って）ほら（待って）
(Wait!) Look! (Wait!)
予想のできない展開に
In an unpredictable development,
ステージは揺れる格別なストーリー
the stage shakes with an exceptional story.
耳を澄ましたら
If you listen closely,
月が踊る
the moon dances
雨粒のハーモニー
to the harmony of raindrops.
浮かぶふわふわな空想
A fluffy fantasy floating up,
暴走？底なしの本能！
running wild? Limitless instinct!
すべて知りたいでしょ
You want to know everything, right?
Hey guys!
叫べ気分は最高？
Shout it out, are you feeling great?
最高！
Great!
Come on!
もっと叫べ気分は最高？
Shout louder, are you feeling great?
最高！
Great!
ポルカ終わるか？
Is Polka over?
終わらない！
It's not over!
It's showtime!
繋いだ手離さないでなんてね
"Don't let go of my hand"... Just kidding!
どうしたって重たくなっちゃって困るわ
I'd be in trouble if it got too heavy.
いつの日かエピローグを一緒に綴ろう
Let's write the epilogue together someday.
きっと約束よ
That's a promise.
Life goes on!
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future awaits.
なんて自由だ！笑っちゃうよ
It's so free! It makes me laugh.
ねえホログラムよりも先へ
Hey, let's go beyond the hologram!
夢のような花舞台に
On a dream-like flower stage,
感情を馳せたら
if you let your feelings soar...
スナップからパッと照らす
Lighting up in a snap,
人生のスポットライト
the spotlight of life.
薔薇色のプレミアショー
A rose-colored premium show!
どこへだって添い遂げたい
I want to be with you wherever we go.
ここが特等席よ！
This is the best seat in the house!
Yeah! Let's go!
あんたにゃもう もったいない
I'm way too good for you!
あたしゃ本当 ナイスバディ
I've got a really nice body!
自分で 言うくらい
Saying it myself,
タダじゃない じゃない じゃない じゃない？
I don't come cheap, do I?
おほほ！
Ohoho!
熱けりゃ 冷ませばいい
If it's hot, just let it cool down
寂しけりゃ エヴリバディ
If you're lonely, everybody...
誰にも わからない
Nobody knows
恋愛って いつ火がつくのか
when love will catch fire
ダイナマイト
Dynamite!
恋はダイナマイト
Love is dynamite!
どんなに 不景気だって
No matter how bad the recession is,
恋はインフレーション
love is in inflation!
こんなに 優しくされちゃ
When you treat me this kindly,
みだら
I'll go wild...
明るい 未来に
In a bright future,
就職希望だわ
I hope to get a job!
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
世界が羨む
the envy of the world!
恋をしようじゃないか!
Let's fall in love!
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
なんだか 物足りない
Somehow, it's not enough
どこにいたって 愛しててほしいわ
No matter where I am, I want you to love me
自分で 伝えるの
Expressing it myself...
恥ずかしい じゃない じゃない じゃない じゃない？
is embarrassing, isn't it?
うぉー！
Wow!
いっそ 二人きりが
I'd rather it just be the two of us
憧れよ エヴリバディ
what we long for, everybody!
誰しも 気づいてない
No one has noticed yet
恋愛って 夢の落とし穴
love is a dream's pitfall
ミステリー
Mystery!
恋はミステリー
Love is a mystery!
こんなの 不自然だって
Even if they say it's unnatural,
恋のインサイダー
we're love insiders!
それでも 上手にされちゃ
Still, if you handle me well,
あらわ
I'm laid bare...
幸せ 来る日も
Even on the days when happiness comes,
キャンセル待ちの
I'm on the waiting list...
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile is...
世界が羨む
the envy of the world!
夢があるじゃないか!
Don't you have dreams?
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
Wake up!
ふわふわふわふわ
Fuwa fuwa fuwa fuwa!
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE マシーン
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE Machine
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE ステーション
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE Station
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE ファクトリー
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE Factory
LOVE, LOVE, LOVE IS WONDERFUL
イェーイ！
Yeah!
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
世界が羨む
the envy of the world!
恋をしようじゃないか!
Let's fall in love!
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
モニカもボスも
Monica and the boss too,
あんたも私も
You and me too,
みんなの社長さんも
And everyone's president too,
Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
ラブマシーン
Love Machine!
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
新曲のお披露目あり！「Glitter Love」
#OmaruPolkaBirthday2026
New song reveal: "Glitter Love"!
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名！
1/30 21:00〜
Polka's live with the most guests ever—10 Holomem guests!
Jan 30, 21:00~